Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم الإدارة، شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪I plant miles of peach blossoms just for her♪
أزرع أميالاً من أزهار الخوخ خصيصاً من أجلها
♪Sweet words bloom upon those branches♪
♪تزهر الكلمات العذبة على تلك الأغصان♪
♪Love runs deep, trapped in longing♪
♪الحب عميق، محاصر في الشوق♪
♪Night listens answers to longing are the most terrifying♪
♪تستمع الليل إلى إجابات الشوق، وهي الأكثر رعباً♪
♪At my fingertips, worries drift and linger♪
♪على أطراف أصابعي، تتلاشى الهموم وتستمر♪
♪Having tasted a moment of carefree joy♪
♪ بعد أن تذوقت لحظة من الفرح الخالي من الهموم ♪
♪Today, I pluck romance and moonlight♪
اليوم، أقطف الرومانسية وضوء القمر
♪And weave them all into a painting♪
♪ واجمعها كلها في لوحة ♪
=The Ultimate Vow, Unknown to You=
=العهد الأسمى، الذي تجهله=
=Episode 7=
=الحلقة 7=
(Chengguang Hall, three days later)
(قاعة تشنغوانغ، بعد ثلاثة أيام)
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Your injuries are no longer serious, are they?
إصاباتك لم تعد خطيرة، أليس كذلك؟
Where is Ru?
أين رو؟
I have led men to search the entire palace.
لقد قُدتُ رجالاً لتفتيش القصر بأكمله.
We found no trace of Young Lady Shen.
لم نعثر على أي أثر للسيدة الشابة شين.
Go find her.
اذهب وابحث عنها.
Yes.
نعم.
The most dangerous place is the safest place.
أخطر مكان هو أكثر الأماكن أماناً.
He actually didn't die.
في الحقيقة لم يمت.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Search thoroughly.
ابحث بدقة.
Yes.
نعم.
Who's there?
من هناك؟
Don't be afraid. It's me.
لا تخف. أنا هو.
General.
عام.
I'll take you away.
سآخذك بعيداً.
This is...
هذا هو...
Su Changji's jade pendant.
قلادة اليشم لسو تشانغجي.
Go to the General's Residence.
اذهب إلى مقر إقامة الجنرال.
(General's Residence)
(مقر إقامة الجنرال)
Your Highness, what are you doing?
يا صاحب السمو، ماذا تفعل؟
Search it.
ابحث عنه.
Yes.
نعم.
Your Highness suddenly brings troops into my residence.
قام صاحب السمو فجأة بإدخال قوات إلى مقر إقامتي.
What is the meaning of this?
ما معنى هذا؟
Young Lady Shen has gone missing.
اختفت الشابة شين.
I heard General Su is hiding her.
سمعت أن الجنرال سو يخفيها.
There is no Young Lady Shen in this residence,
لا توجد السيدة شين الشابة في هذا المسكن،
only the General's wife.
زوجة الجنرال فقط.
Su Changji.
سو تشانغجي.
Don't force me to be unpleasant.
لا تجبرني على أن أكون مزعجاً.
Your Highness, do not go too far.
يا صاحب السمو، لا تذهب بعيداً جداً.
Stop!
قف!
Ru.
رو.
Come back to the palace with me.
عد معي إلى القصر.
Unless I die.
إلا إذا مت.
Ru.
رو.
Come back with me.
عد معي.
The night before last,
الليلة قبل الماضية،
the Crown Prince took the General's wife away.
أخذ ولي العهد زوجة الجنرال بعيداً.
Is it true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
Keep your voice down.
اخفض صوتك.
I heard the General hasn't shown himself for three days.
سمعت أن الجنرال لم يظهر نفسه منذ ثلاثة أيام.
Don't discuss such matters.
لا تناقش مثل هذه الأمور.
Your Ladyship.
سيدتي.
I hear Shen in the prison has been eating quite well.
سمعت أن شين في السجن كان يأكل جيداً.
Your Ladyship, everything is done by the rules.
سيدتي، كل شيء يتم وفقاً للقواعد.
The rules?
ما هي القواعد؟
This is what she should be eating.
هذا ما يجب أن تأكله.
I'm afraid that's improper.
أخشى أن هذا غير لائق.
What's improper about it?
ما هو غير اللائق في ذلك؟
His Highness hasn't come to see her for three days.
لم يأتِ صاحب السمو لرؤيتها منذ ثلاثة أيام.
It was probably just a passing fancy.
ربما كانت مجرد نزوة عابرة.
Does person like her
هل يحبها الشخص؟
deserve fine meals?
هل تستحقون وجبات فاخرة؟
But if His Highness were to find out...
لكن ماذا لو علم صاحب السمو بذلك؟
If you can make her suffer enough,
إذا استطعت أن تجعلها تعاني بما فيه الكفاية،
this will only be the beginning.
هذه ستكون مجرد البداية.
Remember,
يتذكر،
leave no evidence.
لا تترك أي أثر.
Do it well, and there will be greater rewards later.
أتقن عملك، وستحصل على مكافآت أكبر لاحقاً.
Rest assured, Your Ladyship.
اطمئني يا سيدتي.
I understand.
أفهم.
Madam, it's time to eat.
سيدتي، حان وقت تناول الطعام.
Did you bring your own rations?
هل أحضرت معك حصصك الغذائية؟
You're noble and precious.
أنت نبيل وثمين.
I fear this coarse fare
أخشى هذا الطعام الرخيص
is beneath you.
هذا لا يليق بك.
However,
لكن،
His Highness hasn't come to see you for three days.
لم يأتِ صاحب السمو لرؤيتك منذ ثلاثة أيام.
Presumably
من المفترض
he doesn't care what you eat.
لا يهمه ما تأكله.
In that case,
في هذه الحالة،
why not let you taste it first?
لماذا لا ندعك تتذوقه أولاً؟
How dare you!
كيف تجرؤ!
Do you want to die?
هل تريد الموت؟
You...
أنت...
How dare you?
كيف تجرؤ؟
Why wouldn't I dare?
لماذا لا أجرؤ؟
The money your mistress paid you
المال الذي دفعته لك عشيقتك
won't even cover your burial.
لن يغطي حتى تكاليف دفنك.
You...
أنت...
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
Go.
يذهب.
Prepare hot water for a bath,
جهز الماء الساخن للاستحمام،
and a clean set of clothes.
ومجموعة ملابس نظيفة.
This...
هذا...
What?
ماذا؟
Do you want me to decide for you?
هل تريدني أن أقرر نيابةً عنك؟
Yes.
نعم.
I'll do it right away.
سأفعل ذلك على الفور.
What's with all the panic?
ما سبب كل هذا الذعر؟
Your Ladyship.
سيدتي.
Shen Qingru
شين تشينغرو
is not easy to deal with.
ليس من السهل التعامل معه.
Go help in the kitchen.
اذهب وساعد في المطبخ.
She'll be handled here.
سيتم التعامل معها هنا.
Prepare the bath items.
جهزي مستلزمات الحمام.
Remember,
يتذكر،
the water must be cold enough.
يجب أن يكون الماء بارداً بدرجة كافية.
Yes.
نعم.
How's the water temperature?
كيف هي درجة حرارة الماء؟
Your Ladyship.
سيدتي.
If we're going to play, let's play something new.
إذا كنا سنلعب، فلنلعب شيئاً جديداً.
Young Lady Shen,
الشابة شين،
are you satisfied
هل أنت راضٍ؟
with this bath water?
باستخدام ماء الحمام هذا؟
Your Ladyship!
سيدتي!
Why don't you try it yourself?
لماذا لا تجرب ذلك بنفسك؟
Let go of me!
اتركني!
Tie her up!
اربطوها!
Young Lady Shen, with the body of a courtesan,
الشابة شين، بجسد عاهرة،
yet you put on airs as if delicate and noble,
ومع ذلك تتظاهر بالرقة والنبل،
too soft to suffer.
أرق من أن يعاني.
Since that's the case,
وبما أن الأمر كذلك،
I have specially prepared for you
لقد أعددت خصيصاً لك
a lively little spectacle.
مشهد صغير مفعم بالحيوية.
Stop pretending to be so virtuous.
توقف عن التظاهر بالفضيلة.
You're nothing but a shameless, lowly maid.
أنتِ لستِ سوى خادمة وقحة وحقيرة.
Seducing His Highness wasn't enough,
لم يكن إغواء صاحب السمو كافياً،
you even went after General Su.
بل إنك لاحقت الجنرال سو.
Since you're so good at enticing men,
بما أنكِ بارعة في إغواء الرجال،
tonight,
الليلة،
I'll grant your wish.
سأحقق أمنيتك.
Guards!
حراس!
I'd like to see
أود أن أرى
how many men's hearts you can ensnare.
كم عدد قلوب الرجال التي يمكنكِ أن تأسريها؟
Come in.
ادخل.
Wen Ling.
ون لينغ.
You will pay for what you've done today.
ستدفع ثمن ما فعلته اليوم.
Then I'll wait and see.
سأنتظر وأرى.
Enjoy your night of pleasure.
استمتع بليلة من المتعة.
Thank you for the reward, Your Ladyship.
شكراً لكِ على المكافأة، سيدتي.
Little beauty.
جمال صغير.
Let's have some fun tonight.
لنستمتع قليلاً الليلة.
Don't come any closer!
لا تقترب أكثر!